<resources xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools">
    <string name="app_name">HomeClick</string>


    <string name="app_bar">
    <font size="20">HomeClick</font>
    </string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="new_here">I am new here</string>
    <string name="sign_me_in">Sign me in</string>
    <string name="info">Information</string>
    <string name="my_ads">My Ads</string>
    <string name="saved_ads">Saved Ads</string>
    <string name="send_link_in_mail">Send Link In Email</string>
    <string name="age_18">I am 18 years old</string>
    <string name="terms">I agree to the terms and conditions</string>
    <string name="not_signed_in">Not signed in?</string>
    <string name="do_following">Just do the following</string>

    <string name="_full_name">Full Name</string>
    <string name="email">Email Address</string>
    <string name="phone_number">Phone Number</string>

    <string name="Rent">Rent</string>
    <string name="Sale">Sale</string>

    <string name="_available"><font color="#0000">Available</font></string>
    <string name="not_available"><font color='#F44336'>Not available</font></string>


    <string name="floor">Floor</string>
    <string name="floor_space">Floor Space</string>
    <string name="facilities">Facilities</string>
    <string name="gas">Gas</string>
    <string name="security">Security Guard</string>
    <string name="tenant_type">Tenant Type</string>
    <string name="utility">Utility Charge</string>
    <string name="monetary_dealings">Monetary Dealings</string>
    <string name="move_in">Ready To Move In From</string>
    <string name="post_by">Post By</string>
    <string name="rent_out_my_place">Rent Out My Place</string>
    <string name="sell_my_place">Sell My Place</string>
    <string name="remove">Remove</string>
    <string name="any">Any</string>
    <string name="choose_ad_type">CHOOSE AD TYPE</string>
    <string name="enter_maximum_payment_amount">Enter maximum payment amount</string>
    <string name="enter_number_of_bathrooms">Enter number of bathrooms</string>
    <string name="enter_number_of_bedrooms">Enter number of bedrooms</string>
    <string name="apply_filter">APPLY FILTER</string>
    <string name="title_activity_maps">Map</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main">MainActivity</string>
    <!-- Strings used for fragments for navigation -->
    <string name="first_fragment_label">First Fragment</string>
    <string name="second_fragment_label">Second Fragment</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="previous">Previous</string>

    <string name="hello_first_fragment">Hello first fragment</string>
    <string name="hello_second_fragment">Hello second fragment. Arg: %1$s</string>
    <string name="map_view">Map View</string>

    <string name="description">Description</string>
    <string name="date">Date</string>

    <string name="student_or_working_person">Student or Working Person</string>
    <string name="minus">-</string>
    <string name="plus">+</string>
    <string name="security_guard">Security Guard</string>
    <string name="per_month">Per Month</string>
    <string name="outdoor_features">Outdoor Features</string>
    <string name="indoor_features">Indoor Features</string>
    <string name="available_from">Available From</string>
    <string name="add_photos_to_post">Add Photos To Post</string>
    <string name="post">Post</string>
    <string name="previously_added_photos">Previously Added Photos</string>
    <string name="property_condition">Property Condition</string>
    <string name="new_property">New</string>
    <string name="payment">Payment</string>
    <string name="elevator">Elevator</string>
    <string name="generator">Generator</string>
    <string name="garage_space">Garage Space</string>
    <string name="family">Family</string>
    <string name="rent_rate">Rent Rate</string>

    <string name="gas_availability">Gas Availability</string>
    <string name="area_name">Area Name</string>
    <string name="full_address">Full Address</string>
    <string name="full_name">Full Name</string>
    <string name="established">Established</string>
    <string name="asking_amount">Asking Amount</string>
    <string name="email_address">Email Address</string>
    <string name="_description">Description</string>
    <string name="bedrooms">Bedrooms</string>
    <string name="bathrooms">Bathrooms</string>
    <string name="balconies">Balconies</string>
    <string name="this_information_can_only_be_seen_by_members">This information can only be seen by members.</string>

    <string name="information_can_only_be_seen_by_members">Information can only be seen by members.</string>
    <string name="personal_information">Personal Information</string>
    <string name="add_location">Add Location</string>
    <string name="location">Location</string>
    <string name="_full_address">Full Address</string>
    <string name="rent">Rent</string>
    <string name="_two">2</string>
    <string name="__2">2</string>
    <string name="_2_">2</string>
    <string name="floor_no">Floor No</string>
    <string name="_5">5</string>
    <string name="_1400sqt">1400 sqt</string>
    <string name="available">Available</string>
    <string name="_10000_bdt" tools:ignore="ExtraTranslation">1000 BDT</string>
    <string name="_5000_bdt">5000 BDT</string>
    <string name="_18_07_2021">18/07/2021</string>
    <string name="_1300_sqt">1300 SQT</string>
    <string name="home_click">HomeClick</string>
    <string name="terms_of_use">Terms Of Use


    </string>


    <string name="welcome">

        Welcome to HomeClick!
    </string>

    <string name="Terms_of_use">
        These Terms of Use(or "Terms") govern your use of HomeClick, except where
        we expressly state that separate terms(and not these) apply, and provide
        information about the HomeClick service(the “Service”), outlined below.
        When you create an HomeClick account or use HomeClick, you agree to
        these terms.
        \n\n
        <b>The HomeClick Service</b>
        \n\n We agree to provide you with
        the HomeClick Service.The Service includes
        all of the HomeClick products, features,applications,services,technologies
        and software that we provide to advance HomeClick\'s mission:
    </string>
    <string name="ToLet"><b>
       To Let &#160;:</b>\nThe Landlord agrees to let to the Tenant and the Tenant agrees to take a tenancy of
        the house.Neither the property nor any part  of the Property will be used at any time
        during the term of this agreement by Tenant for the purpose of business,profession
        or trade of any kind, or for the purpose other than Tenant\'s;only or principal private
        single-family residence.
        \n\n
        <b>Sell &#160;:
        \n
        </b>The Landlord sell house to the Tenant.Furthermore things you have to solve by yourself
        by contacting each other.
        \n\n<b>
        Tenant Improvements &#160;:\n
        </b>The Tenant will obtain written information before doing any of the following  &#160;: &#160; \n
        - &#160;Applying Adhesive materials,or inserting nails or hooks in walls or ceilings other than
        two small picture hook per wall.\n
        - &#160; Painting,redecorating or in anyway significantly altering the appearance of The Property


    </string>


    <string name="policy">
        <b>Your Commitments</b>\n
        In return for our commitment to provide the Service, we require you to make the below commitments to us.\n\n
        <b>Who Can Use HomeClick.</b>\nWe want our Service to be open and inclusive as possible, but we also want it to be
        safe,&#160; secure,&#160;and in accordance with the law. So, we need you to commit to a few restrictions in order to be part of the HomeClick community.\n\n
        &#8226;  &#160;You must be at least 18 years old or the minimum legal age in your country to use HomeClick.\n
        &#8226;  &#160;You must not be prohibited from receiving any aspect of our Service under applicable laws or engaging in payments
        related Services if you are on an applicable denied party listing.\n\n

        <b>How You Can\'t Use HomeClick.</b>\nProviding a safe and open Service for a broad community requires that we all do our part.\n\n
        &#8226;  &#160;<b>You can\'t impersonate others or provide inaccurate information.</b>\n
         You don\'t have to disclose your identity on HomeClick, but you must provide us with accurate and
         up to date information (including registration information), which may include providing personal data.
         Also, you may not impersonate someone or something you are not, and you can\'t create an account for someone else
         unless you have their express permission.\n
         &#8226;  &#160;You can\'t do anything unlawful, misleading, or fraudulent or for an illegal or unauthorized purpose.
         &#8226;  &#160;You can\'t violate (or help or encourage others to violate) these Terms or our policies,
        including in particular the HomeClick Community Guidelines.\n\n

       &#8226;  &#160;<b>You can’t sell, license, or purchase any account or data obtained from us or our Service.</b>\n
        This includes attempts to buy, sell, or transfer any aspect of your account (including your username);
        solicit, collect, or use login credentials or badges of other users; or request or
        collect HomeClick usernames, passwords, or misappropriate access tokens.\n\n
        &#8226;  &#160;<b>You can\'t post someone else’s private or confidential information without permission
        or do anything that violates someone else\'s rights, including intellectual property rights
        (e.g., copyright infringement, trademark infringement, counterfeit, or pirated goods).</b>\n
        You may use someone else\'s works under exceptions or limitations to copyright and related rights under applicable law.\n
        You represent you own or have obtained all necessary rights to the content you post or share. Learn more,
        including how to report content that
        you think infringes your intellectual property rights, here.\n
         &#8226;  &#160;You can\’t modify, translate, create derivative works of, or reverse engineer our products or their components.\n
         &#8226;  &#160;You can\'t use a domain name or URL in your username without our prior written consent.\n\n


        <b>Updating These Terms</b>\n
         We may change our Service and policies, and we may need to make changes to these Terms so that they accurately
         reflect our Service and policies. Unless otherwise required by law, we will notify you (for example, through our Service)
        before we make changes to these Terms and give you an opportunity to review them before they go into effect.
        Then, if you continue to use the Service, you will be bound by the updated Terms. If you do not want to agree
        to these or any updated Terms, you can delete your account, here.


    </string>

    <string name="go_back">Go Back</string>

    <string name="data_policy">

        <font size = "13">This policy describes the information we process to support HomeClick features.</font>\n\n<b><font size = "15"> What kinds of information do we collect? </font> </b>\n To provide the HomeClick Products, we must process information about you.
        The types of information we collect depend on how you use our Products.Information and content you provide. We collect the content,
        communications and other information you provide when you use our Products, including when you sign up for an account,
        create or share content or communicate with others. This can include information in or about the content you provide (like metadata),
        such as the location of a post or the date a file was created.Our systems automatically process content and communications you
        and others provide to analyze context.\n\n<b><font size = "15">Device Information</font></b>\nWe collect information from and about
        the computers, phones, connected TVs and other
        web-connected devices you use that integrate with our Products, and we combine this information
        across different devices you use. For example, we use information collected about your use of our Products on your phone
        to better personalize the content (including ads) or features you see when you use our Products on another device,
        such as your laptop or tablet, or to measure whether you took an action in response to an ad we showed you on your phone
        on a different device.\n\n<b><font size = "15">Promote Safety, integrity and security</font></b>\n
        Password Less  SignIn/SignUp\n\n<b><font size = "15">Communicate with you.</font></b> \nWe use the information we have to send you marketing communications,
        communicate with you about our Products,and let you know about our policies and terms. We also use your information
        to respond to you when you contact us.\n\n<b><font size = "15">How can I manage or delete information about me?</font></b>\n
      We provide you with the ability to access, rectify, port and erase your data.
      We store data until it is no longer necessary to provide our services or until your account is deleted -
        whichever comes first. This is a case-by-case determination that depends on things like the nature of the data,
        why it is collected and processed, and relevant legal or operational retention needs.\n\n<b><font size = "15">How will we notify you of changes to this policy?</font></b>\n We\'ll notify you before we make changes to this policy
        and give you the opportunity to review the revised policy before you choose to continue using our Products.

    </string>
    <string name="send_location">Send Location</string>


</resources>